<resources>

    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Category name for phrases [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_attractions">Attractions</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for colors [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_places">Places</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for numbers [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for family members [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_sports">Sports</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome to Lahore \n A City of Gardens</string>

    <!-- strings contains attractions -->
    <string name="title_sozo">Sozo Water Park</string>
    <string name="title_safari">Lahore Zoo Safari</string>
    <string name="title_museum">Lahore Museum</string>
    <string name="title_bagh">Bagh-e-Jinnah</string>
    <string name="title_gulshan">Gulshan-e-Iqbal Park</string>
    <string name="title_jilani">Jilani Park</string>
    <string name="title_joyland">Joyland</string>
    <string name="title_unicorn">Unicorn Gallery</string>
    <string name="title_sindbad">Sindbad</string>
    <string name="title_shakir">Shakir Ali Museum</string>
    <string name="sozo_description">Sozo Water Park is a water park located in Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan. It is one of the few water-themed amusement parks in the city. You will love it.It is a point of interest. There are three pools in this park.</string>
    <string name="lahore_zoo_safari">The Woodland Wildlife Park was established in 1982 over 242 acres as a government funded public facility. In 1998, it was handed over to the Punjab Wildlife and Parks Department by the Forest Department. </string>
    <string name="lahore_museum">The Lahore Museum, was originally established in 1865-66 on the site of the hall or building of the 1864 Punjab Exhibition and later shifted to its present site located on The Mall, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan in 1894.</string>
    <string name="bagh_e_jinnah">Bagh-e-Jinnah is a historical park in the city of Lahore, Pakistan. It was formerly known as Lawrence Gardens. Today, the large green space contains a botanical garden, Masjid Dar-ul-Islam, and Quaid-e-Azam Library situated in a Victorian building.</string>
    <string name="gulshan_e_iqbal">The Gulshan-e-Iqbal Park is a large park and recreational space in Lahore, Pakistan. With an area of over 67 acres, the park is one of the largest in the city. It is situated in the suburban locality of Allama Iqbal Town.</string>
    <string name="jilani_park">Jilani Park is located in the city of Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan. It is on the Jail Road in front of the Services Hospital. It is famous for its floral exhibitions and artificial waterfall. Annual horse racing competitions are held in this park.</string>
    <string name="joyland">Joyland is an amusement park in Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan. The park, adjacent to Fortress Stadium, was established in 1977 and is one of the largest recreation parks in the city. It is spread out over an area of 6 acres.</string>
    <string name="unicorn_gallery">Unicorn Gallery is an art gallery in Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan. Unicorn Gallery was set up in 2004. Unicorn Gallery was inaugurated by the Governor of the State Bank, Dr Ishrat Husain.</string>
    <string name="sindbad">Operating in Lahore since 1991, under the umbrella of the Dolmen Group, Sindbad’s Wonderland is a household name and a pioneer in the family entertainment industry of Pakistan. Having served two generations of Pakistani children, Sindbad attributes its success to maintaining high standards and constant innovation throughout the years.</string>
    <string name="shakir_ali_museum">Shakir Ali Museum or Official Birthplace of Artist Shakir Ali was a family home museum in Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan. The museum was inaugurated after the death of famous artist and painter Shakir Ali\'s death.</string>

    <!-- Strings contains places -->
    <string name="title_shalimar">Shalimar Gardens</string>
    <string name="title_badshahi">Badshahi Mosque</string>
    <string name="title_fort">Lahore Fort</string>
    <string name="title_wazir">Wazir Khan Mosque</string>
    <string name="title_minar">Minar-e-Pakistan</string>
    <string name="title_sheesh">Sheesh Mahal</string>
    <string name="title_moti">Moti Masjid</string>
    <string name="title_jallo">Jallo Park</string>
    <string name="title_hiran">Hiran Minar</string>
    <string name="title_darbar">Data Durbar Complex</string>
    <string name="title_delhi">Delhi Gate</string>
    <string name="title_mochi">Mochi Gate</string>
    <string name="title_hazuri">Hazuri Bagh</string>
    <string name="shalimar_gardens">The Shalimar Gardens, sometimes spelled Shalamar Gardens, is a Mughal garden complex located in Lahore, capital of the Pakistani province of Punjab.</string>
    <string name="badshahi_mosque">The Badshahi Mosque is a Mughal era mosque in Lahore, capital of the Pakistani province of Punjab. The mosque is located west of Lahore Fort along the outskirts of the Walled City of Lahore.</string>
    <string name="lahore_fort">The Lahore Fort, is a citadel in the city of Lahore, Pakistan. The fortress is located at the northern end of Lahore\'s Walled City, and spreads over an area greater than 20 hectares</string>
    <string name="wazir_khan_mosque">The Wazir Khan Mosque is a Mughal era mosque in the city of Lahore, capital of the Pakistani province of Punjab.</string>
    <string name="minar_e_pakistan">Minar-e-Pakistan is a public monument located in Iqbal Park which is one of the largest urban parks in Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan.</string>
    <string name="sheesh_mahal">The Sheesh Mahal is located within the Shah Burj block in northern-western corner of Lahore Fort. It was constructed under the reign of Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan in 1631-32</string>
    <string name="moti_masjid">Moti Masjid, one of the "Pearl Mosques", is a 17th-century religious building located inside the Lahore Fort. It is a small, white marble structure built by Mughal emperor Shah Jahan, and is among his prominent extensions to the Lahore Fort Complex.</string>
    <string name="jalo_park">Jallo Park, established in 1978, is a public recreation and wildlife site located in Lahore District, Punjab, Pakistan.</string>
    <string name="hiran_minar">Hiran Minar is set in peaceful environs near Lahore in a town called Sheikhupura, Pakistan. It was constructed by the Mughal Emperor Jahangir as a monument to Mansiraj, his favourite pet deer or antelope</string>
    <string name="data_darbar_complex">Data Darbar, located in the city of Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan is one of the oldest Muslim shrines in South Asia. It houses the remains of a Sufi saint, Abul Hassan Ali Hajvery. He is said to have lived on the site in the 11th century.</string>
    <string name="delhi_gate">The Delhi Gate is one of the six remaining gates which were the traditional entry points into the Walled City of Lahore in Lahore, Pakistan. Delhi Gate and the adjacent Shahi Hammam were restored in 2015 by the Aga Khan Cultural Service Pakistan.</string>
    <string name="mochi_gate">The Mochi Gate locally known as Mochi Darwaza is located within the Walled City of Lahore in Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan. Mochi Gate is a historical gate built by the Mughals.</string>
    <string name="hazzuri_bagh">Hazuri Bagh is a garden in Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan, bounded by the Lahore Fort, Badshahi Mosque, the Samadhi of Ranjit Singh and the Roshnai Gate. In the center stands the Hazuri Bagh Baradari, built by Ranjit Singh.</string>

    <!-- Strings contains food -->
    <string name="title_lassi">Fiqay Ki Lassi</string>
    <string name="title_paaye">Nasir kai Paaye</string>
    <string name="title_kebab">Bhaiya kai Kebab</string>
    <string name="title_bashir">Bashir Darul Mahi</string>
    <string name="title_puri">Taj Puri Wala</string>
    <string name="title_hareesa">Amritsari Hareesa</string>
    <string name="title_falooda">Riaz Falooda</string>
    <string name="title_nisbat">Nisbat Road Kai Gol Gappay</string>
    <string name="title_karahi">Butt ki karhai</string>
    <string name="title_nishat">Nishat Takatak</string>
    <string name="title_nafees">Nafees Dahi Bhalay</string>
    <string name="title_nihari">Waris Nihari</string>
    <string name="title_kulfa">Benazir Kulfa</string>

    <string name="fiqay_ki_lassi">Fiqay ki lassi is claimed to be the best lassi there is to be offered in Lahore. Their classic peray wali lassi is so popular, that regardless of whatever time you go there you’d have to take a token and wait in a significantly long queue. Rest assured, it\’s totally worth the wait.</string>
    <string name="nasir_k_paaye">Who doesn\’t love some paaye (trotters for the angraiz qoum)? Nasir bhai makes the finest paaye you will find in Lahore. Though, they’re in a close competition with Phajay kai paaye but we recommend you try Nasir. Phaja is too mainstream.</string>
    <string name="bhaiya_k_kebab">If you crave for some spicy and tasty Lahori kebab, chances are you wouldn’t have to travel much further. Bhaiya is located in Model Town. Beware, like with everything else that gets famous, due to the success of the kebab place, you\’ll find many doppelgangers with the exact same name nearby.</string>
    <string name="bashir_darul_mahi">It\’s winters, and what better than to kick it off with some freshly fried fish! Bashir Darul Mahi (literally, Bashir’s House of Fish) has been around for ages, it’s probably been there before you were even born and the business is still booming like anything. Go, give it a try.</string>
    <string name="taj_puri_wala">If you aren\’t into halwa puri ka nashta for Sundays you don\’t have the right to call yourself a Lahori. So give Taj a try to fall in love with what amazingness Lahore has to offer. Located right opposite Badshai masjid, you get to have a true Lahori breakfast and gaze out into the mesmerizing historic site that is older than most of Lahore itself.</string>
    <string name="amritsari_hareesa">For all the modern Lahoris, you might call it the step sister of Haleem, but it’s also drastically different in a great way! Located at Nisbat Road near Lakshmi Chowk, a two-floor building with probably not the fanciest or hygienic of environments but boy do they serve some good Hareesa.</string>
    <string name="riaz_falooda">If you\’ve had enough of waffles, hot chocolate and crêpes and you’re looking to try something different, possibly more entertaining and delicious, then Riaz Falooda is your place. Located in Anarkali, the falooda bowl by Riaz contains kulfa, ice and those slimy yet oh-so-refreshing noodles. It will truly be like a taste of heaven itself.</string>
    <string name="nisbat_road">Those crunchy vessels of fried goodness that hold chanay and yogurt and all sorts of other chatpatti delicacies. You pick one, you dip them in the refreshingly cold khatta, maybe another dip in the meetha and pop them in your mouth before they explode all over yourself. Mouthwatering, just talking about them. This particular vendor is located right next to Lakhsmi Chowk opposite Amritsari Hareesa.</string>
    <string name="butt_ki_karashi">Located at Lakshmi Chowk, the place offers you the finest chicken, halalofied (Sacrificed) right in front of you, which is a comforting news considering you’re not really sure about other “chicken” karahis anymore. A word of caution, just like Bhaiya kai Kebab this too has many doppelgangers; you literally rely on old folk tales to spot the right one!</string>
    <string name="nishat_takatak">Situated right next to Gulistan Cinema, the clanking of the chopping of mutton brain into a gooda that looks rather strange but surprisingly delicious! You can enjoy the brain masala with their famous mint chutney, yes the perfect foodie evening awaits you! Another plus: everything\’s so minced that it doesn\’t really matter what you\’re served as long as it tastes good</string>
    <string name="nafees_bhalay">Situated in Model Town, Nafees Dahi Bhalay has made quite a name for itself with one of its most loyal customers being the Prime Minister himself. And we all that Mr. Sharif know his food, so better get in line for some tangy dahi bhalay by Nafees.</string>
    <string name="waris_nihari">There is meat and then there is Nihari meat. This slow cooked beef curry is truly a delicacy which can be tried any time of the day with some freshly made Naans! Waris Nihari is drenched in oil, but this doesn’t stop people lining up to have a taste of it. And you would be surprised by the various varieties of Nihari – ranging from simple Nihari to Tawa fried.</string>
    <string name="benazir_kulfa">Who doesn’t like ice cream? And kulfa is the Pakistani version of ice cream. With those crunchy nuts giving it an edgy texture to compliment the sheer sweetness of the kulfa itself. And to get the best kulfa Lahore has to offer, head on down to main market and order some at Benazir Kulfa. While you\’re at it, you might want to give their equally decadent kheer a try too.</string>

    <!-- Strings contains sports -->
    <string name="title_gaddafi">Gaddafi Stadium</string>
    <string name="title_hockey">National Hockey Stadium</string>
    <string name="title_academy">Aleem Dar Cricket Academy</string>
    <string name="title_dha">DHA Sports Complex</string>
    <string name="gaddafi_stadium">Gaddafi Stadium is a cricket ground in Lahore, Pakistan. It was designed by famous architect and engineer Nasreddin Murat-Khan, and constructed by Mian Abdul Khaliq and Company in 1959.</string>
    <string name="national_stadium">National Hockey Stadium is a purpose-built field hockey stadium in Lahore, Pakistan. It is the biggest field hockey stadium in the world. The stadium has a capacity of 45,000 spectators.</string>
    <string name="aleem_dar">Aleem Dar Cricket Academy Near LDA Office, Behind Mian Plaza Johar Town، Lahore، Pakistan</string>
    <string name="DHA_sports_complex">In order to generate maximum sports activities establishment of the Sports Academy / Club are in the offing. This will help enhance the participation of residents in outdoor healthy activities and create sports culture especially in DHA. Training of young players will act as a nursery for their further grooming at national level and raise the standards of sports in DHA.</string>
    <string name="toast_message">Unable to retrieve selected category</string>
    <string name="attractions_positions">attractions_position</string>


</resources>
